A Guide to the Spelman Fund of New York records FA063
Rockefeller Archive Center
Spelman Fund of New York records
1922-1970
Rockefeller Archive Center
Spelman Fund
FA063
38 Cubic Feet 100 document cases
Arrangement note
This collection is arranged in six series, as follows:
Series 1 - Minutes, Dockets, and Documents of Record
Series 2 - Administration
Series 3 - Finances
Series 4 - Projects
Series 5 - General Files
Series 1015 - Photographs
Biographical/Historical note
The Spelman Fund of New York was chartered as a corporation on December 27, 1928, exclusively for "charitable, scientific and educational purposes including the advancement and diffusion of knowledge concerning child life, the improvement of interracial relations and cooperation with public agencies."
$10,000,000 was provided for The Spelman Fund by the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial shortly after the latter organization merged with The Rockefeller Foundation in 1929. The Memorial had developed a broad program in child study and interracial relations. Though the Fund continued to support some of the agencies previously supported by the Memorial for the duration of the particular grant, the main program of the Fund was in the area of public administration and intergovernmental relations. This was an area the Memorial had just begun to develop in its program, and it soon became the primary interest of the Fund. The Fund worked to improve the technical aspects of public administration. They supported activities which would improve exchange of technical information and experience and also activities of research to discover improved methods and techniques of organization.
Many major appropriations were made to the "1313" agencies, i.e., the American Association of Public Welfare Officials, the American Legislators Association, the American Municipal Association, the American Public Welfare Association, the American Public Works Association, the American Society of Planning Officials, the Civil Service Assembly, the Council of State Governments, the Federation of Tax Administrators, the International City Managers Association, the Municipal Financial Officers Association, the National Association of Housing Officials, the Public Administration Clearing House and the Public Administration Service. These groups were brought together in Chicago in 1932, and later in a building on the campus of the University of Chicago. The address was 1313 E. 60th Street, hence the name.
The final grant of unexpended funds was made to the Public Administration Clearing House, the nerve center of the "1313" agencies, and in 1949 the Fund was dissolved.
The Spelman Fund Collection covers the period from 1928 to 1949.
Scope and Contents note
Important subjects in this collection include federal-state cooperation/relations, interstate cooperation/relations, standards in public administration on all levels, and training of public officials.
Among the correspondents are:
American Legislators' Association
Henry Toll
American Municipal Association
Carl Chatters
Earl Mallery
Clifford Ham
Paul Betters
American Public Welfare Association
Fred Hoehler
Frank Bane
American Public Works Association
Donald Stone
American Society of Planning Officials
Walter Blucher
Civil Service Assembly
William Brownrigg
Charles Messick
Clifford Amsden
Council of State Governments
Frank Bane
Henry Toll
Mark Graves
Federation of Tax Administrators
Albert Lepawsky
International City Managers Association
Donald Stone
Louis Brownlow
Municipal Financial Officers Association
Mines B. Phillips
Carl Chatters
National Association of Housing Officials
Charles Ascber
Public Administration Clearing House
Louis Brownlow
Charles Ascber
Joseph Willits
Public Administration Service
Louis Brownlow
Donald Stone
Winthrop Aldrich
Kenneth Chorley
William E. Dodd
William Tudor Gardiner
Robert M. Hutchins
Fiorello LaGuardia
Lewis Meriam
Charles Merriam
Guy Moffett
Francis Perkins
John D. Rockefeller 3rd
Beardsley Ruml
Harold Stassen
Charles P. Taft II
Lent D. Upson
Leonard White
Arthur Woods
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IV 2B 06
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The papers of The Spelman Fund were deposited with The Rockefeller Foundation Archives in 1948 by The Spelman Fund.
Public policy; State governments -- United States; Federal government -- United States
- Minutes, Dockets and Documents of Record, 1927-1949; 1
  Scope and Contents note
  All are mimeographed copies, though the minutes are signed.
  Spelman Fund of New York Minutes Index
  A card index to the Spelman Fund of New York records, Series 1: Minutes, Dockets and Documents of Record is available for researcher use. Referenced entries in the SFNY Minutes are indicated by a 5-digit number, formatted as a 2-digit year and 3-digit page number, on the left edge of the cards. For example: "31032" = 1931 Minutes, page #032.
  Both Blue and white cards must be read to have a complete picture of any action recorded in the Minutes. Every action is recorded on the white cards; but only those actions having to do with appropriations are recorded on the blue cards.
  The SFNY Minutes Index is located in drawers 65-71 of the 72-drawer cabinet next to the RAC's reading room.
  - Minutes, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Minutes, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minutes, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Minutes, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Minutes, 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Minutes, 1947-1949 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Dockets, 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Dockets, January-November 1930 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Dockets, December 1930 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Dockets, January-April 24, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Dockets, April 31-December 1931 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Dockets, January-April 19, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Dockets, April 19-December 1932 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Dockets, March-April 1933 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Dockets, May-December 1933 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Dockets, January-April 1934 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Dockets, May-July 1934 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Dockets, October-December 1934 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Dockets, February-April 1935 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Dockets, May 1935 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Dockets, June-December 1935 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Dockets, January-April 1936 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Dockets, May 1-11, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Dockets, May 25-December 1936 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Dockets, January-April 1937 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Dockets, May 5, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Dockets, May 17-December 1937 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Dockets, January-May 9, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Dockets, May 24, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Dockets, June-December 1938 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Dockets, January-May 5, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Dockets, May 12-June, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Dockets, September-December 1939 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Dockets, January-May 1940 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Dockets, June-December 1940 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Dockets, February-June 13, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Dockets, June 30-December 1941 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Dockets, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Dockets, May-July 1943 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Dockets, November 1943 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Dockets, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Dockets, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Dockets, May 1946 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Dockets, August-November 1946 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Dockets, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Dockets, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Documents of Record, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Documents of Record, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Documents of Record, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Documents of Record, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Documents of Record, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Documents of Record, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Documents of Record, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Documents of Record, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Documents of Record, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Documents of Record, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Documents of Record, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Documents of Record, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Documents of Record, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Documents of Record, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Documents of Record, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Documents of Record, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Documents of Record, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Documents of Record, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Documents of Record, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Documents of Record, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Documents of Record, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Documents of Record, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Documents of Record, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Documents of Record, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Documents of Record, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Documents of Record, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Documents of Record, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Documents of Record, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Documents of Record, 1929-1932 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Documents of Record, 1933-1934 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Documents of Record, 1935-1936 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Documents of Record, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Documents of Record, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Documents of Record, 1939-1940 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Documents of Record, 1941-1945 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Documents of Record, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1928-1934 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1935-1941 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1942-1949 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Administration, 1928-1950; 2
  This series contains information on the administrative side of The Spelman Fund including declinations, personnel information, counsel's opinions, general policy, inter-office memoranda and general correspondence.
  - Certificate of Incorporation and Bylaws (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence, 1928-1933 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Counsel, 1928-1931 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Counsel, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Counsel, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Counsel, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Counsel, 1938-1943 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Counsel, 1944-1949 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Declinations (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Executive Committee, 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Executive Committee, 1936-1941 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Executive Committee, 1942-1947 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Memoranda, 1929-1935 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Memoranda, 1936-1946 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Policy, 1928-1930 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Policy, 1931-1941 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Policy - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Policy - Child Study (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Policy - Cooperation with Government Agencies (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Grant, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Grant, 1936-1939 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Grant, 1940-1946 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Trustees, 1929-1937 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Trustees, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Trustees, 1940-1943 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Trustees, 1944-1948 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Personnel (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Personnel (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Personnel (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Personnel - Staff Assistance (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Current By-Laws (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1929-1939 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1940-1949 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1937 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, 1940 and 1941 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report, 1942 and 1943 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Final Report, 1949; Copy 1 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Final Report, 1949; Copy 2 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Final Report, 1949; Copy 3 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Finances, 1928-1950; 3
  This series includes the ledgers, journals, and cash books, as well as audits and correspondence pertaining to various securities held by the Fund, income tax information, and occasional grants.
  - Audits, 1929-1932 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Audits, 1933-1936 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Audits, 1937-1941 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Audits, 1942-1947 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Authorizations - Appropriations, 1930-1948 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Authorizations - Signatures, 1928-1943 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1932-1942 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Baltimore Trust Company, 1934-1942 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Bonds in Default, 1933-1942 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Budgets, 1929-1936 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Budgets, 1937-1948 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway, 1936-1942 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway, 1933-1943 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Dissolution (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Erie Railroad, 1928-1941 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Finance Committee, 1932-1939 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Finance Committee Minutes, 1929-1948 (Box 2, Folder 140A)
  - Financial Procedure (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Financial Report, 1929-1931 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Financial Report, 1932-1934 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Financial Report, 1935-1937 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Financial Report, 1938-1940 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Financial Report, 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Financial Report, 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Financial Report, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Great Island Research Associates, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Group Insurance (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Guarantees, 1931-1933 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Guardian National Bank of Detroit, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Home Insurance Company, 1929-1940 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Illinois Central Railroad, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Income Tax Exemption (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Income Tax, Federal - Employees (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Income Tax, State (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Medical Service (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1933-1942 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - New York Power and Light Corporation, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - New York State Unemployment Insurance, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Northern State Power Company Bonds, 1930-1937 (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Parents Publishing Association, 1929-1930 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Railroad Investment Survey, 1939-1941 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Retaining Fee (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Retiring Allowance (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Retiring Allowance (A-Z) (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Grant, 1938-1943 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Securities, 1933-1941 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Securities - Access (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Securities - Market Value, 1934-1936 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Securities - Market Value, 1937-1948 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Southern Railway Company, 1931-1933 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - St. Louis, Iron Mountain and Southern Railway, 1931-1947 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - St. Louis, San Francisco Railway, 1932-1945 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - St. Louis, Southwestern Railroad, 1932-1942 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - St. Paul, Minneapolis and Manitoba Railroad, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Standard Oil of New Jersey, 1932-1938 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - State University of Iowa, 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Surplus and Deficiency Fund, 1931-1948 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Tax and Capital Stock, 1933-1935 (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - Trust Agreements (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - U.S. Daily Publishing Corporation, 1931-1934 (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Union Guardian Trust, 1935-1941 (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Union Guardian Trust, 1942-1950 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - University of Minnesota, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 185A)
  - Cash Book, 1929-1940 (Box 7, Folder 185B)
  - Cash Book, 1941-1949 (Box 7, Folder 185C)
  - Journal, 1928-1948 (Box 7, Folder 185)
  - Securities Ledger, 1929-1948 (Box 7A, Folder 185E)
  - Securities Ledger, 1929-1946 (Box 7A, Folder 185)
  - Securities Ledger, 1929-1948 (Box 7A, Folder 185E)
  - Securities Ledger, 1929-1946 (Box 7A, Folder 185)
  - Ledger, 1928-1949 (Box 8, Folder 185G)
  - Trial Balance, 1928-1945 (Box 8, Folder 185H)
  - Trial Balance, 1946-April 1949 (Box 8, Folder 185I)
- Projects, 1925-1970; 4
  Arrangement note
  This series is arranged in two subseries:
  Subseries 1 - General Projects
  Subseries 2 - "1313" Organizations
  Project files include correspondence, audits, reports, publications, bulletins and newsletters.
  Spelman Fund of New York Project Files and General Files Index
  A card index to the Spelman Fund of New York records, Series 4: Projects, and Series 5: General Files is available for researcher use. Project files and General files are indicated by the alphabetically arranged file titles in Series 4 and 5.
  The SFNY Project Files and General Files Index is located in drawers 67-71 of the 72-drawer cabinet next to the RAC's reading room.
  - Projects - General Projects, 4.1
    Project files are arranged alphabetically.
    - American Committee for the International Union of Local Authorities, 1930-1935 (Box 1, Folder 186)
    - American Committee for the International Union of Local Authorities, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 187)
    - American Committee for the International Union of Local Authorities, January-June 1938 (Box 1, Folder 188)
    - American Committee for the International Union of Local Authorities, July-December 1938 (Box 1, Folder 189)
    - American Committee for the International Union of Local Authorities, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 190)
    - American Section of the International Institute of Administrative Sciences, 1929-1934 (Box 1, Folder 191)
    - American Section of the International Institute of Administrative Sciences, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 192)
    - American Section of the International Institute of Administrative Sciences, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 193)
    - American Section of the International Institute of Administrative Sciences, 1939-1941 (Box 1, Folder 194)
    - Brookings Institute - Indian Affairs, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 195)
    - Brookings Institute - Indian Affairs, 1930-1933 (Box 2, Folder 196)
    - Brookings Institute - Municipal Affairs Service, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 197)
    - Bureau of Public Personnel Administration, 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 198)
    - Bureau of Public Personnel Administration, January-April 1930 (Box 2, Folder 199)
    - Bureau of Public Personnel Administration, May-December 1930 (Box 2, Folder 200)
    - Bureau of Public Personnel Administration, January-June 1931 (Box 2, Folder 201)
    - Bureau of Public Personnel Administration, July 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 202)
    - Bureau of Public Personnel Administration - Audits, 1929-1931 (Box 2, Folder 203)
    - Bureau of Public Personnel Administration - Reports (Box 2, Folder 204)
    - Bureau of Social Hygiene, 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - Cambridgeshire County Council, 1928-1933 (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio, January-April 1936 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio, May-December 1936 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio, January-May 1938 (Box 3, Folder 214)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio, June-December 1938 (Box 3, Folder 215)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 216)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio, 1940-1947 (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio - Audits, 1936-1938 (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio - Annual Reports, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 219)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio - Annual Reports, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 220)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio - Reports (Box 4, Folder 221)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio - Reports (Box 4, Folder 222)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio, Copy 1 (Box 5, Folder 222A)
    - Committee on Coordination and Cooperation in Hamilton County, Ohio, Copy 2 (Box 5, Folder 222B)
    - Council on Intergovernmental Relations, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Council on Intergovernmental Relations, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Council on Intergovernmental Relations, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Council on Intergovernmental Relations, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Council on Intergovernmental Relations, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Council on Intergovernmental Relations, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Council on Intergovernmental Relations, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Council on Intergovernmental Relations, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Council on Intergovernmental Relations, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Council on Intergovernmental Relations - Reports and Publications (Box 6, Folder 232)
    - Department of Welfare - Virginia, 1932-1934 (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - Fellowships - Spelman Fund (Box 6, Folder 234)
    - Fellowships - Rockefeller Foundation Reappointments (Box 6, Folder 235)
    - Fellowships - Bane, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 236)
    - Fellowships - Belsley, 1936-1937 (Box 6, Folder 237)
    - Fellowships - Betters, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 238)
    - Fellowships - Blucher, 1935-1937 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - Fellowships - Brownlow, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 240)
    - Fellowships - Bunbury, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 241)
    - Fellowships - Carr, 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 242)
    - Fellowships - Chatters, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - Fellowships - Didisheim, 1936-1937 (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - Fellowships - Egger, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 245)
    - Fellowships - Eliot, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 246)
    - Fellowships - Gibbon, 1932-1933 (Box 7, Folder 247)
    - Fellowships - Gulick, 1931-1934 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - Fellowships - Ham, 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - Fellowships - Hill, 1934-1942 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - Fellowships - Hoan, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - Fellowships - Hoehler, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - Fellowships - Larsson, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - Fellowships - May, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - Fellowships - Merriam, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - Fellowships - Morris, 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 256)
    - Fellowships - Rana, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 257)